{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647953740","data":{"timestamp":" 947647953739"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063214"," gameId":" e0630445-348b-4485-8029-eca5d7ba34c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kamba ya kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HII"," userResponse":" HII"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647954959","data":{"timestamp":" 947647954959"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063214"," gameId":" e0630445-348b-4485-8029-eca5d7ba34c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kamba ya kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647956956","data":{"timestamp":" 947647956956"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063214"," gameId":" e0630445-348b-4485-8029-eca5d7ba34c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kamba ya kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMBA"," userResponse":" KAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647956959","data":{"timestamp":" 947647956959"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063214"," gameId":" e0630445-348b-4485-8029-eca5d7ba34c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kamba ya kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647963271","data":{"timestamp":" 947647963271"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063214"," gameId":" e0630445-348b-4485-8029-eca5d7ba34c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kamba ya kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KURUKA"," userResponse":" HII"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647965764","data":{"timestamp":" 947647965764"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063214"," gameId":" e0630445-348b-4485-8029-eca5d7ba34c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hii ni kamba ya kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647965919","data":{"timestamp":" 947647965919"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063214"," gameId":" e0630445-348b-4485-8029-eca5d7ba34c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kamba ya kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KURUKA"," userResponse":" HII"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647974418","data":{"timestamp":" 947647974417"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063214"," gameId":" c78cfe38-6b6e-41a1-b918-7450c782db27"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647974640","data":{"timestamp":" 947647974640"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063214"," gameId":" c78cfe38-6b6e-41a1-b918-7450c782db27"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647975603","data":{"timestamp":" 947647975603"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063214"," gameId":" c78cfe38-6b6e-41a1-b918-7450c782db27"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647976886","data":{"timestamp":" 947647976886"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063214"," gameId":" c78cfe38-6b6e-41a1-b918-7450c782db27"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647979789","data":{"timestamp":" 947647979787"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063214"," gameId":" c78cfe38-6b6e-41a1-b918-7450c782db27"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647980632","data":{"timestamp":" 947647980632"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063214"," gameId":" c78cfe38-6b6e-41a1-b918-7450c782db27"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647980945","data":{"timestamp":" 947647980945"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063214"," gameId":" c78cfe38-6b6e-41a1-b918-7450c782db27"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647982178","data":{"timestamp":" 947647982178"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063214"," gameId":" c78cfe38-6b6e-41a1-b918-7450c782db27"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647985659","data":{"timestamp":" 947647985659"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063214"," gameId":" c78cfe38-6b6e-41a1-b918-7450c782db27"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647986641","data":{"timestamp":" 947647986641"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063214"," gameId":" c78cfe38-6b6e-41a1-b918-7450c782db27"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647986893","data":{"timestamp":" 947647986893"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063214"," gameId":" c78cfe38-6b6e-41a1-b918-7450c782db27"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647987836","data":{"timestamp":" 947647987836"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063214"," gameId":" c78cfe38-6b6e-41a1-b918-7450c782db27"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647990656","data":{"timestamp":" 947647990656"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063214"," gameId":" c78cfe38-6b6e-41a1-b918-7450c782db27"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647991689","data":{"timestamp":" 947647991689"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063214"," gameId":" c78cfe38-6b6e-41a1-b918-7450c782db27"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647992162","data":{"timestamp":" 947647992162"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063214"," gameId":" c78cfe38-6b6e-41a1-b918-7450c782db27"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647996753","data":{"timestamp":" 947647996752"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063214"," gameId":" c78cfe38-6b6e-41a1-b918-7450c782db27"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947647996807","data":{"timestamp":" 947647996807"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063214"," gameId":" c78cfe38-6b6e-41a1-b918-7450c782db27"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.corr.ltr.stim:story_1.punc.1.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648020419","data":{"timestamp":" 947648020419"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063214"," gameId":" a052c74f-8328-43ae-b30b-e58575f023a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.corr.ltr.stim_story_1.punc.1.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Rangi ya sita ni nili "," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.corr.ltr.stim:story_1.punc.1.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648021154","data":{"timestamp":" 947648021154"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063214"," gameId":" a052c74f-8328-43ae-b30b-e58575f023a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.corr.ltr.stim_story_1.punc.1.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Rangi ya sita ni nili "," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.corr.ltr.stim:story_1.punc.1.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648035709","data":{"timestamp":" 947648035709"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063214"," gameId":" a052c74f-8328-43ae-b30b-e58575f023a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.corr.ltr.stim_story_1.punc.1.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Rangi ya sita ni nili "," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.corr.ltr.stim:story_1.punc.1.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648047384","data":{"timestamp":" 947648047384"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063214"," gameId":" a052c74f-8328-43ae-b30b-e58575f023a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.corr.ltr.stim_story_1.punc.1.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Rangi ya sita ni nili "," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.corr.ltr.stim:story_1.punc.1.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648057064","data":{"timestamp":" 947648057063"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063214"," gameId":" a052c74f-8328-43ae-b30b-e58575f023a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.corr.ltr.stim_story_1.punc.1.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Rangi ya sita ni nili "," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.corr.ltr.stim:story_1.punc.1.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648065072","data":{"timestamp":" 947648065071"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063214"," gameId":" a052c74f-8328-43ae-b30b-e58575f023a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.corr.ltr.stim_story_1.punc.1.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Rangi ya sita ni nili "," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.corr.ltr.stim:story_1.punc.1.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648074521","data":{"timestamp":" 947648074521"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063214"," gameId":" a052c74f-8328-43ae-b30b-e58575f023a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.corr.ltr.stim_story_1.punc.1.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Rangi ya sita ni nili "," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_2"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.corr.ltr.stim:story_1.punc.1.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648080824","data":{"timestamp":" 947648080824"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063214"," gameId":" a052c74f-8328-43ae-b30b-e58575f023a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.corr.ltr.stim_story_1.punc.1.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Rangi ya sita ni nili "," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.corr.ltr.stim:story_1.punc.1.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648094359","data":{"timestamp":" 947648094358"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063214"," gameId":" a052c74f-8328-43ae-b30b-e58575f023a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.corr.ltr.stim_story_1.punc.1.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_Rangi ya sita ni nili "," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648105963","data":{"timestamp":" 947648105963"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063214"," gameId":" 006f0be8-5d0f-4f70-b24a-9d54f084f785"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_8-9-5"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 9"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648116507","data":{"timestamp":" 947648116507"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063214"," gameId":" 006f0be8-5d0f-4f70-b24a-9d54f084f785"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-4-9"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 9"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648125724","data":{"timestamp":" 947648125724"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063214"," gameId":" 006f0be8-5d0f-4f70-b24a-9d54f084f785"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-4-9"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648137329","data":{"timestamp":" 947648137328"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063214"," gameId":" 81873896-45a3-4880-9c88-6211b9763e16"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu anafahamu kuwa tembo ana mkonga mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648139124","data":{"timestamp":" 947648139124"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063214"," gameId":" 81873896-45a3-4880-9c88-6211b9763e16"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu anafahamu kuwa tembo ana mkonga mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648141203","data":{"timestamp":" 947648141203"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063214"," gameId":" 81873896-45a3-4880-9c88-6211b9763e16"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu anafahamu kuwa tembo ana mkonga mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAFAHAMU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648142969","data":{"timestamp":" 947648142969"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063214"," gameId":" 81873896-45a3-4880-9c88-6211b9763e16"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu anafahamu kuwa tembo ana mkonga mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648145020","data":{"timestamp":" 947648145020"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063214"," gameId":" 81873896-45a3-4880-9c88-6211b9763e16"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu anafahamu kuwa tembo ana mkonga mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEMBO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648146756","data":{"timestamp":" 947648146755"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063214"," gameId":" 81873896-45a3-4880-9c88-6211b9763e16"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu anafahamu kuwa tembo ana mkonga mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648149620","data":{"timestamp":" 947648149620"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063214"," gameId":" 81873896-45a3-4880-9c88-6211b9763e16"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu anafahamu kuwa tembo ana mkonga mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKONGA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648151304","data":{"timestamp":" 947648151304"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063214"," gameId":" 81873896-45a3-4880-9c88-6211b9763e16"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu anafahamu kuwa tembo ana mkonga mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MREFU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648153365","data":{"timestamp":" 947648153365"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063214"," gameId":" 81873896-45a3-4880-9c88-6211b9763e16"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapo kale pua la tembo lilikuwa fupi na nono."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648155934","data":{"timestamp":" 947648155934"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063214"," gameId":" 81873896-45a3-4880-9c88-6211b9763e16"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapo kale pua la tembo lilikuwa fupi na nono."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648158501","data":{"timestamp":" 947648158500"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063214"," gameId":" 81873896-45a3-4880-9c88-6211b9763e16"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapo kale pua la tembo lilikuwa fupi na nono."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648160762","data":{"timestamp":" 947648160762"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063214"," gameId":" 81873896-45a3-4880-9c88-6211b9763e16"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapo kale pua la tembo lilikuwa fupi na nono."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648164935","data":{"timestamp":" 947648164935"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063214"," gameId":" 81873896-45a3-4880-9c88-6211b9763e16"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapo kale pua la tembo lilikuwa fupi na nono."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648168038","data":{"timestamp":" 947648168038"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063214"," gameId":" 81873896-45a3-4880-9c88-6211b9763e16"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapo kale pua la tembo lilikuwa fupi na nono."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEMBO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648168182","data":{"timestamp":" 947648168182"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063214"," gameId":" 81873896-45a3-4880-9c88-6211b9763e16"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Lakini hapo kale pua la tembo lilikuwa fupi na nono."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648168311","data":{"timestamp":" 947648168311"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063214"," gameId":" 81873896-45a3-4880-9c88-6211b9763e16"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapo kale pua la tembo lilikuwa fupi na nono."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEMBO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648177295","data":{"timestamp":" 947648177295"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063214"," gameId":" a25a375b-10bc-42a4-afa2-f926f5ed4678"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648177518","data":{"timestamp":" 947648177518"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063214"," gameId":" a25a375b-10bc-42a4-afa2-f926f5ed4678"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648178481","data":{"timestamp":" 947648178481"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063214"," gameId":" a25a375b-10bc-42a4-afa2-f926f5ed4678"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648179754","data":{"timestamp":" 947648179754"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063214"," gameId":" a25a375b-10bc-42a4-afa2-f926f5ed4678"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648182623","data":{"timestamp":" 947648182623"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063214"," gameId":" a25a375b-10bc-42a4-afa2-f926f5ed4678"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648183466","data":{"timestamp":" 947648183466"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063214"," gameId":" a25a375b-10bc-42a4-afa2-f926f5ed4678"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648183779","data":{"timestamp":" 947648183779"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063214"," gameId":" a25a375b-10bc-42a4-afa2-f926f5ed4678"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648185012","data":{"timestamp":" 947648185011"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063214"," gameId":" a25a375b-10bc-42a4-afa2-f926f5ed4678"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648188486","data":{"timestamp":" 947648188486"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063214"," gameId":" a25a375b-10bc-42a4-afa2-f926f5ed4678"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648189469","data":{"timestamp":" 947648189469"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063214"," gameId":" a25a375b-10bc-42a4-afa2-f926f5ed4678"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648189722","data":{"timestamp":" 947648189722"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063214"," gameId":" a25a375b-10bc-42a4-afa2-f926f5ed4678"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648190675","data":{"timestamp":" 947648190675"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063214"," gameId":" a25a375b-10bc-42a4-afa2-f926f5ed4678"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648193478","data":{"timestamp":" 947648193478"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063214"," gameId":" a25a375b-10bc-42a4-afa2-f926f5ed4678"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648194511","data":{"timestamp":" 947648194511"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063214"," gameId":" a25a375b-10bc-42a4-afa2-f926f5ed4678"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648194984","data":{"timestamp":" 947648194984"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063214"," gameId":" a25a375b-10bc-42a4-afa2-f926f5ed4678"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648199541","data":{"timestamp":" 947648199541"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063214"," gameId":" a25a375b-10bc-42a4-afa2-f926f5ed4678"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648199600","data":{"timestamp":" 947648199600"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063214"," gameId":" a25a375b-10bc-42a4-afa2-f926f5ed4678"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}